<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" /><updated>2024-06-08T22:58:18+00:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">=][=</title><author><name>PaintsPlastic</name></author><entry><title type="html">The Body in the Wall</title><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/2024/06/08/the-body-in-the-wall.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Body in the Wall" /><published>2024-06-08T09:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-06-08T09:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:4000/2024/06/08/the-body-in-the-wall</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://0.0.0.0:4000/2024/06/08/the-body-in-the-wall.html"><![CDATA[The young man fidgeted in the cold metal chair, he didn't seem to know what to do with his hands.

He was scrawny, his scruffy black hair  and he barely came up to the Imperial Aquila's proudly displayed on the chests of the two officers wielding shotguns stood either side of the door to the interview room. The young mans green eyes moved around the room, he looked at the two giants by the door, their all black uniforms. The only other occupant of the room sat across the table opposite him, partially shrouded in darkness.

The clock on the wall, the sole decoration on the black walls, ticked, although it displayed no time.

"Am I in trouble, m'Lord?" said the young man, breaking the painful silence in the room.

The man sat opposite him didn't answer immediately. He closed a file he had been thumbing through, and lit a lo-stick. The man was big, not as big as the men by the door, but still big, and he was clearly in charge here. 

"That very much depends on what else you tell us" he said. His tone was flat and monotone, expressing no emotion or excitement, but the words seemed to hang in the young mans head after they'd been spoken, like an echo.

That made the young man fidget even more, and the rising panic behind his eyes would have been clear even to those not versed in the arts of spotting the subtlety of human behaviour such as the man who sat opposite him.

"Let's start with a name shall we?" said the man through a cloud of exhaled smoke.

"A name m'Lord?" said the young man.

"Yes a name. Let's start with your name, if you have one. What do they call you?" came the response.

"Karha, m'Lord"

"OK, Karha, I would like you to explain to me why you are here" said the man.

Karha stopped fidgeting as he processed what he had just been asked to do, now he just sat looked puzzled for a moment.

"Because I was brought here by the troopers m'Lord" he said.

The man sat opposite him blew out a cloud of smoke. But said nothing, any expression hidden in the shroud of darkness that covered his face.

Tick, tick, tick - the clock on the wall seemed to get louder in the silence.

"I mean, er, well that is to say, I reported something and then they brought me here m'Lord"

"What did you report?" came the monotone voice.

"M'Lord, I found a- a man, in the- the walls m'Lord"

"You found a man, in the walls?"

"Yes m'Lord" 

"Please elaborate"

"Sorry, m'Lord?"

The man exhaled another breath of lo-stick smoke.

"Please tell me more about 'the man in the walls', Karha"

"Oh, yes m'Lord, of course" said Karha, the fidgeting was back, but the sheer panic in his eyes had begun to fade slightly, only to be replaced with a fear of upsetting the man who sat opposite him.

"So I came in from temple this mornin, m'Lord, and the landlady she usually hangs all the washing out on the walkways but she went and put it all up the stairs. She was so mad when I tried to tip-toe cross it m'Lord" Karha chuckled slightly at that particular memory but from the silence that echoed back from the opposite side of the table he sensed the joke was lost on the man "so anyways m'Lord I had to go round back of the habs and use the old entrance. The door sticks y'see m'Lord, need to kick it to get it open, and I guess I grew up a bit since I last went that way an I hit it a bit too hard. The door made a hole in the wall, I was about to run off before the landlady came, but then I saw him in there m'Lord."

"Him?"

"Yes m'Lord, I don't know who he was but he was a him"

The man stubbed out the lo-stick and lit another, Karha tried to see the mans face through the dim light of the firelighter. All he made out was a thick beard and a bald head.

"Please continue, Karha, what else can you tell me about this man?"

"m'Lord, he looked like he might have had some money, from what I could see from his clothes, but he was stuffed in there pretty good m'Lord, bent up in all kinds of ways"

"When you say 'bent up', Karha, what exactly do you mean?"

"He was all bent and snapped m'Lord, he must have done something bad to make someone do that do him", Karha said, his curious mind fishing for some sort of clarification of his supposition. When no response came, he continued. "er, that is to say m'Lord, that the wall he was in was not big it was about like, this size".

Karha made a gesture with both hands as if to estimate the rough side of the wall cavity in which the body had been found concealed in. Roughly the size of a mans head, the man noted, taking another draw on the freshly lit lo-stick.

"Did you see anyone around, Karha? Anyone hanging around the habs lately that might know more about why this man showed up in the walls?"

"No m'Lord, not anyone that I saw, not lately, specially not since the troubles started, everyone keeps themselves to themselves these days m'Lord"

"Indeed" said the man in shadow.

"Thank you, Karha, I think that will be all for the moment. You will remain here with us for the time being to answer any more questions we might have.

"Sergeant" he said without turning "please escort the young man to a one of our more comfortable holding cells and see that he is given something to eat"

"By your will My Lord" came the reply.

The two men burly men forward and Karha stood to follow them, but hesitated.

"m'Lord, may I ask a question?" said Karha.

"You may" said a voice from the shadow.

"m'Lord, forgive me, but what will happen to the person what put the man in the wall?"

The man leaned forwards into the light, his thick black beard was well trimmed but covered much of his face and his bald head shone from the glare off the single light above the table. He looked tough, that's what Karha thought, old and tough, and he had a big scar on his cheek.

"They will be punished, as are all who are found guilty"



---]]></content><author><name>PaintsPlastic</name></author><category term="grimdark" /><category term="inq28" /><category term="3458-decima" /><category term="featured" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The young man fidgeted in the cold metal chair, he didn’t seem to know what to do with his hands.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://0.0.0.0:4000/assets/img/grimdark1.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://0.0.0.0:4000/assets/img/grimdark1.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">The Black Bishop</title><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/2024/06/06/the-black-bishop.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Black Bishop" /><published>2024-06-06T09:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-06-06T09:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:4000/2024/06/06/the-black-bishop</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://0.0.0.0:4000/2024/06/06/the-black-bishop.html"><![CDATA[++ CONNECTION ESTABLISHED ++

++ USER AUTHENTICATED ++ 

++ WELCOME: LORD INQUISITOR ++

++ BEGIN DECRYPTION SEQUENCE ++

++ ENCRYPTION PROTOCOL: SIGMA-5921-BETA-2:22.1.3 +++

++ SECURE LINK ESTABLISHED +++

++ MESSAGE BEGINS ++

God Emperors Blessings on you, My Lord, I hope that this message finds you in good health.

It is with much humility and with The Will of the God Emperor guiding my hand, that I am pleased to report the utter destruction of the cult known as "The Crippled Hand", a devious collective comprised of no individuals of significant note aside from their leader, an individual particularly well versed in Warp craft and the summoning of Daemons. I personally led the team and witnessed the summary execution of all known members of the cult after all information was extracted from the individuals that my team spared for that purpose. It seems that they were intent on bringing about a lesser warp being via ritual sacrifice, the full details of the purgation of this sect can be found in my full report which you will find attached to this missive. My continuing investigations into cult activity on the planet designated 3458-Decima has turned up an anomaly that I thought worthy of bringing to your attention.

During visits to speak to various informers and knowledgeable individuals in search of futher cult activity I had begun to hear rumours of an individual perpetrating the most heinous of crimes. The identity of the individual is unknown to me, but it seems the local traders and citizens refer to an individual called "The Black Bishop". As best I can determine the name is derived from the reported mannerisms of the individual as well as their clothing, which are both described from various sources as "That of a Holy Man".

This individual seemingly haunts the ruins of the industrial areas of 3458-Decima, the area known locally as "the blocks". They do not seem to have any preferential targets, as the bodies that appear strung to the piping and walkways hail from many backgrounds and as yet I have not been able to determine any link between the victims aside from the typically horrific ultimate fate, and the presence of a particular brand they each bore somewhere about their person. The places in which the brand has been found vary with the levels of flesh still remaining on each victim. Of the bodies that I have seen with my own eyes, if you told me that they had been mauled by some ancient beast of legend, aside from the ridiculousness of the idea it would not cause me to doubt your sanity. I will not regale Your Lordship with descriptions of the states in which some of the victims have been found in, save to say that a certain xenos race would potentially baulk at the sights I have borne witness to while investigating this "Black Bishop".

But the brand, My Lord, the brand is what drew my attention to this case initially as there is nothing obviously ritualistic about the killings, other than the gruesome manner in which they are despatched and ultimately displayed. But to mark each victim in such a way smacks of dark dealings.

The brand is burned into the flesh of each victim by unknown means. The brand itself has something of the Warp about it, I've not seen anything quite like it before and cannot link it to any known cult or practice. An pict image is included along with this missive for your records and the hope that the greater resources available to Your Lordship will be able to identify it.

It must be stressed that there are no reports of "attacks", My Lord. There are only reports of killings. It seems that anyone that encounters this individual does not survive to tell their tale.

With Your Lordships blessing I will continue my investigation into this individual in an attempt to uncover their true identity and any links they may have to further cult elements on 3458-Decima.

The Emperor Protects.

Your faithful servant,
Inquisitor Jorge

++ MESSAGE ENDS ++

++ SECURE LINK TERMINATED ++

++ CONNECTION CLOSED ++]]></content><author><name>PaintsPlastic</name></author><category term="grimdark" /><category term="inq28" /><category term="3458-decima" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[++ CONNECTION ESTABLISHED ++]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://0.0.0.0:4000/assets/img/blanche1.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://0.0.0.0:4000/assets/img/blanche1.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">The Ruin of Hilarion</title><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/2024/04/25/ruin-of-hilarion.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Ruin of Hilarion" /><published>2024-04-25T09:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-04-25T09:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:4000/2024/04/25/ruin-of-hilarion</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://0.0.0.0:4000/2024/04/25/ruin-of-hilarion.html"><![CDATA[Nestled within the Hazeroth Abyss in the Calixis Sector lies the Agri-world of Hilarion. 

It is home to approximately 750,000,000 Imperial Citizens. 

Ruled by the Council of Seven Colours, Hilarion is a relatively poor world even by Imperial standards and is not well known outside of the Hazeroth Abyss.

Access to the planet is strictly controlled by the PDF and Imperial Navy.


---

Magos Biologus Miena Kohh.

Magos on a sanctioned dig finds some ancient archeo-tech (Necron in origin although they have no idea that it's Necron, as far as they know it's just an ancient race) - this was a tomb world, but there was an accident and none of the Necron on this planet will ever awaken, but nobody knows this.

They begin excavation of the site.

A report is sent to the local offices to confirm a finding.

Criminal elements intercept the report and send mercenaries to secure the finding. (they bypass the trade-quarantine zone implying significant resources)

The Magos and their team are murdered by the mercenaries.

The mercenaries steal the artifact and return it to their patron.

Turns out, that the artifact is a weapon of devastating power.

The patron plans to use it.

End of Part 1.

Part 2 is where our Inquisitor enters the picture.

Part 3 is where the Inquisitor kills the mercenaries patron... except they don't because a Deathmark pops out of an oubliette and kills them, and then the Inquisitor has to try and make sense of what is going on (and that leads into the rest of the world building) 

---

Miena Kohh was a handsome woman in her late 120's, although the extensive but subtle juvenant treatments gave her the physical appearance of a woman of around 40 standard years. She loved her work, and she had over the years built up her team of adjutants, each member brought their own specialist knowledge and skills to the team. This was the first time she'd been to Hilarion, and frankly she couldn't wait to leave.

"What a backwards little world this is" she thought to herself as she carefully brushed dust off the latest finding from the dig site. The site, known as B7-4X-Epsilon to the administration, was referred to by the locals simply as "The Rough", due to the craggy terrain that made it difficult to traverse in vehicles. Were it not for the dig site Miena would never have any reason to visit a place like this. Hilarion was an Agri world, home to around 750,000,000 Imperial Citizens, though most of them were ignorant of that particular fact.

And what a dig it was. This was going to be the one that put her in the history books, an ancient race previously unknown to the Imperium had left it's mark on this world, and her team had extracted a number of items from within what appeared to be a vault made from a polished black stone. The site had been discovered by a local worker who had been hiding from his duties, the worker had of course been disciplined for neglecting their work, Miena didn't like to think what that punishment might have been.

The prize of the dig so far had been a long casket, made from the same polished black stone as the walls of the vault. Measuring around 2 metres it Strange sigils and images were carved into the black stone in astonishing detail and clarity, whomever had made this was a craftsman of the most precise nature. From the initial auspex readings the measurements of the casket were, well precise didn't quite manage to convey the quality of the work.

"Mistress, there are some men approaching" said Thesias, one of her adjutants stirring her from her thoughts.

Miena Kohh might have spent most of her life in academia but she knew danger when she saw it and these men were very clearly dangerous.

The leader of the group, a burly bearded man wearing black carapace armour swaggered towards Miena and her adjutants with the confidence of a man who knows his own worth in a combat situation. Following him was a group of at least 15 men, brutes to a man, most with short cropped or shaved heads of hair, all carrying weapons.

"Who's in charge here?" said the bearded man in a voice that sound like it was being filtered through gravel.

"That would be me" said Miena, putting aside her excavation tools and brushing the dust off her robe as she rose to greet the newcomers.

"So that would make you..." the bearded man paused to query a dataslate attached to his wrist "... Magos Biologus Miena Kohh?"

"Yes, that's correct" replied Miena, "is there some sort of a problem?"

The bearded man didn't reply, he made a few short sharp hand gestures and his men began to fan out around the dig site.

Miena was not used to being ignored. 

"Excuse me, but who are you people and what are you doing here?" demanded Miena, taking a step towards the bearded man.

"How many of you are working this site, Mistress Kohh?" replied the bearded man, ignoring the question.

"Including myself, there are eight of us, plus 3 servitors" replied Miena.

The bearded man nodded, again consulting the dataslate on his wrist, the information Miena had just provided seemed to confirm whatever he was reading.

"Mistress, do you know if there are any additional personnel on the site other than those in your party?" said the bearded man.

"No, this is a sanctioned excavation, only myself and my adjutants are permitted to be here, is there some sort of trouble?" replied Miena.

The bearded man again ignored her question and said something into a vox attached to his carapace armour.

"I asked if there was a problem, sir?" said Miena, struggling to keep the panic out of her voice.

"No problem, Mistress, that all checks out" said the bearded man.

"Oh good, then would you kindly explain what it is you are doing here?" said Miena, feeling a surge of confidence.

The bearded man didn't respond, 

"Primus, we've accounted for all personnel" said a stocky man with a shaved head.

The bearded man, Primus, nodded.

"Man of few words this one" thought Miena.

"Excuse me, Primus, is it?" said Miena.

"I demand to know what you and your men are doing here. This is a sanctioned archaeological dig, I have authorization from the Governor himself" she said, reaching into a pocket to retrieve the dataslate containing the letter of Marque.

The stocky man stood with Primus brought his weapon up, some sort of autocannon from what Miena could tell, she wasn't a military type

"Slowly please, Mistress"

Miena felt her heart begin to race, who were these men, and why were they pointing weapons at her? She slowly removed the dataslate from her robes and presented it to Primus.

"As you can see, it's all been signed off by the local magistrate on behalf of the Governor" gesturing to the dataslate.

Primus nodded.

"Indeed it has, Mistress"





---

The first shot made Mienas heart skip a beat. It was so loud.

She saw the body of Selethica, one of the newest members of her team fall limply to the floor, a large portion of the back of her head turned into a fine mist by a shot from one of the autocannons borne by Primus and his men.

That first shot was quickly followed by a second, and a third, and a fourth... each shot accompanied by another of her team falling to the floor with various parts of their head missing.

Miena struggled in Primus' grip but he was far stronger than her, and her efforts were all but futile.

She watched as one of Primus' men methodically walked along the line of her adjutants, placing a single shot into the head of each one before moving to the next. Most of the adjutants were in a complete state of shock, some had defecated themselves, some were crying, all but Thesias, where was Thesias?

Thesias had been one of her favourites, he'd only recently joined but he was strong minded, highly intelligent, brimming with wit, and quite the handsome young man with his thick dark hair and wide shoulders, and quite the lover. He had been the one to alert her to the approaching men, and she didn't remember seeing him after that. Where had he gone? Had they taken him somewhere?

---

"That's some good work, lad" said Primus pulling a credit chit from his pocket.

Thesias took the proffered credit chit.

"Thank you Primus, I do what is needed"

"There'll be plenty more work for lads with your brains if you're up to it"

"Of course Primus, I do what is needed"

Primus didn't like Thesias, he was a devious little thing, when news of the finding at the dig site had been intercepted Thesias had been given the task of embedding himself within Miena Kohh's survey team and assessing any additional items of value, and ultimately guiding the kill-team in. The boy had serious brains, but a ruthless streak that belied his good looks and soft brown eyes, a dangerous combination, thought Primus.

"Was mistress Kohh suspicious at all?"

"No" replied Thesias.

"Mistress Kohh was more concerned with my physical attributes than anything else"

Primus didn't like that answer at all, it was one thing embedding within the survey team, but another thing to become Kohh's lover. The levels of deception made his skin crawl. He might have been a mercenary, and he often took money from people who he loathed, but he had always prided himself on being a soldier, paid to do a job, in and out, no emotions no questions. Thesias had crossed a line, but the patron was happy, and Primus wasn't the one who would have to live with the deception.

"That's good I suppose, at least we didn't get any trouble of any of the adjutants"

"That'll be all for now, lad, go see Soren and pick up your gear"

Thesias nodded. "Primus", then left the little office that Primus used without closing the door.]]></content><author><name>PaintsPlastic</name></author><category term="grimdark" /><category term="inq28" /><category term="hilarion" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nestled within the Hazeroth Abyss in the Calixis Sector lies the Agri-world of Hilarion.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://0.0.0.0:4000/assets/img/blanche2.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://0.0.0.0:4000/assets/img/blanche2.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">A Grimdark Journey V</title><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/2024/04/18/grim-darkness-part-v.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Grimdark Journey V" /><published>2024-04-18T15:42:45+00:00</published><updated>2024-04-18T15:42:45+00:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:4000/2024/04/18/grim-darkness-part-v</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://0.0.0.0:4000/2024/04/18/grim-darkness-part-v.html"><![CDATA[<p>“In the grim darkness of the 41st Millennium, there is only war”</p>]]></content><author><name>PaintsPlastic</name></author><category term="grimdark" /><category term="inq28" /><category term="featured" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[“In the grim darkness of the 41st Millennium, there is only war”]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://0.0.0.0:4000/assets/img/grimdark1.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://0.0.0.0:4000/assets/img/grimdark1.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">A Grimdark Journey VI</title><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/2024/04/18/grim-darkness-part-vi.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Grimdark Journey VI" /><published>2024-04-18T15:42:45+00:00</published><updated>2024-04-18T15:42:45+00:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:4000/2024/04/18/grim-darkness-part-vi</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://0.0.0.0:4000/2024/04/18/grim-darkness-part-vi.html"><![CDATA["In the grim darkness of the 41st Millennium, there is only war"]]></content><author><name>PaintsPlastic</name></author><category term="grimdark" /><category term="inq28" /><category term="3458-decima" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[“In the grim darkness of the 41st Millennium, there is only war”]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://0.0.0.0:4000/assets/img/grimdark1.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://0.0.0.0:4000/assets/img/grimdark1.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">A Grimdark Journey</title><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/2024/04/18/grim-darkness.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Grimdark Journey" /><published>2024-04-18T15:42:45+00:00</published><updated>2024-04-18T15:42:45+00:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:4000/2024/04/18/grim-darkness</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://0.0.0.0:4000/2024/04/18/grim-darkness.html"><![CDATA["In the grim darkness of the 41st Millennium, there is only war"]]></content><author><name>PaintsPlastic</name></author><category term="grimdark" /><category term="inq28" /><category term="3458-decima" /><category term="featured" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[“In the grim darkness of the 41st Millennium, there is only war”]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://0.0.0.0:4000/assets/img/grimdark1.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://0.0.0.0:4000/assets/img/grimdark1.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>